Good evening friends so here we are with the
last question of the day this is a new set
of the question and in this you have only two hours
left to give your answers and
get a chance to win a prize so here is the
question you have hired a cab and observe
that the cab driver is continuously using the
phone while
driving what would you do do nothing as
driving is his job and advise him not
to use the phone while driving
advise him to park the car and take the
call and last but not the least discuss the
advantage of the
GPS so as you saw this is our
last question of the day this is the last of our five
questions and that is
if you hire a cab you have
booked a cab and you observe that the
cab driver is continuously
using the phone while driving then what will you do now
you will not do anything because the
Driving is his job or you
will advise him not to use the phone
while driving or you
will advise him to park the car
and then take the call or you will talk to him
about the advantages of GPS and all those things so
now you have only two hours left, this is the
last question, this is your last chance
today to
participate in it, the
results of this quiz are going on,
today was our third day and every day we
give you five questions on a daily basis, every
two hours our anchors come and share
a new
question with you, by participating in which you
can win a very exciting gift for yourself and your family
members, we are requesting you that not only you
alone, you can advise all your family members, your
friends to
participate in it
and the interesting part is that you can
participate in all five questions, there is nothing like that
If you attempt
one question in a day, you
cannot attempt the next one, of course you
can, and you have a chance to
win more than one gift in a day. So we
welcome you to come on board and participate.
Participation is not just for gifts,
this
participation is for you; you are contributing towards
road safety,
and you can become a part of this entire campaign, you can become a
part of this road safety by
participating in it,
and this will continue till February 18. Every
day, every two hours, you will get five questions, that is,
every two hours, you will get one question.
You have to answer five questions
and you can win many different
prizes
which are a concern of road safety. Like we talk about
road safety or the cabs that we
book on a daily basis, it is
very important to take care of things.
Whenever you are driving a cab yourself, or a
driver is
driving, or you have taken a cab, then
wearing seat belts is a must.  Very important
seat belt is not that only the
person sitting in front should wear seat belt,
it is very important that you too, if
you are sitting in the back seat, should wear seat belt
because if there is a crash, then the
pressure that is there is a
motion of the belt while
driving, so you are also in that motion, so
if in these cases by mistake a crash happens
or anything happens, then the person sitting in the back seat will be harmed, as well as the person in
front can also be harmed,
so it is better that whenever you sit in the car,
whether you are sitting in the front or you are sitting in the back seat,
always wear the seat belt and
lock it properly
and all these safety gear safety
measures are not just for you, that is, you have to
wear it to show off to someone or it is
for your safety and you should follow these things
for yourself as well and you should
also suggest to your family members or your friends that they should
also
follow all these safety measures,
you can see them  The
question is visible on my screen: You have hired a
cab and observed that the cab driver is
continuously using the phone while driving.
You have hired a cab, you have booked a cab
and you noticed that this cab
driver is continuously using the phone
while driving, what will you do?
In such a situation, do not do anything as
driving is his job, you will not do anything
because driving is his job,
not yours. Or you advise him not to
use the phone while driving. Or
you will advise him that please do
not use the phone while driving.
Advise him to park the car and take a
call. Or you will advise him to
park his car and then
take a call. Discuss the advantages of GPS. Or
you will talk to him about the advantages of GPS.
Join us and
answer this and win an exciting prize
and the result will be given to us in the evening.
Meaning, bluntly.
Bluntly Bluntly Speaking show airs on
our channel at 10 pm at night. You can join it
and the winners are announced in it. You
can see for yourself if you have
won any prize. You can join us at 10 pm and
see your results
or you
can also check the results by going to our website. The results that come
out are five questions on a daily basis.
Each question changes every two hours.
After a question is asked, for example, suppose a
question comes at 9:00 am,
its entries will be closed by 11 am. At 11:00 am,
our anchor comes and gives you a new
question. Similarly, these questions change every two hours. So,
you can be a part of it and win. The
interesting thing is that you can
participate again in all five questions on a daily basis.  And
this show of ours will run till 18th February,
so we are requesting you to come along
with your family, your friends, your
loved ones, us you care about, come and join.
Now there are gifts to be won, but it is
for you to understand and increase
and enhance your knowledge related to road
safety. Road safety because
we are all somehow connected to the roads.
We have to use the roads somewhere or the other, even if it is for some work.
So the main purpose
of this entire camp is to make our roads safe and
we can make it safe only when we follow all the rules. When
we have enough knowledge about what
we should do when and how we should do it.
To enhance our skills,
join us and answer all these interesting
questions.
You know that while driving, it is very important for a
driver who is driving. It is important for
him to
remain focused and avoid doing anything that is distracting
like talking on the phone or using the
phone.
Whatever the driver is doing or the screen that
is installed and some pictures or
songs are playing in it, then it can
become a cause of distraction or if
your
companion is
also with you, if he supposedly falls asleep
or is behaving in a certain way or if you have
a child sitting in the front with you
and he is distracting you, then the
chances of accidents
increase a lot, so we suggest
that a driver should not do any such things
or should not have any such companion with him
which
increases the level of distraction and anything can go wrong,
you must have heard this slogan which is that if your
eyes are diverted, an accident happens, so
being a driver, you should be very focused
on the road and drive,
that is why it is said
that this question of yours is somehow
related to this only, you can see
as it is written in it that you have hired a
cab and observe that the cab driver is
continuously  Using phone while driving
You have booked a cab, you have hired a cab
and after sitting in the cab you noticed that the
driver who was driving was
continuously talking on the phone or using the phone, so if
he is using the phone then what would you suggest,
what would you do at that time, you do nothing as
driving is his job, you will
not do anything because driving is
his job or advise him not to use phone
while driving, you will tell him,
you will tell him not to use the phone
while driving it is not safe and advise
him to park the car and take a call, you will
also advise him to park the
car on the side and then take the call
or discuss the advantages of GPS, you will
talk to him about GPS or
tell him its benefits, so it is your call,
you have to tell what you will do at that time
and by giving your correct answer you can
become a winner, you can win different gifts which are your
safety measures, you have a
chance, come and join your
family  Friends,
we would just suggest to you that
distracted driving is very unsafe
because distraction
increases the chances of mishaps and in the
campaign we are in, we are just
promoting how we can
make you and our roads safe. The
results of this cause can be seen on
our show Bluntly
Speaking at 10 pm and they are
announced in it. You can come and join us at 10 pm and see the results that will be announced
in that show.
Now come and join us with your family and friends
for the day. This is the last
question. You will have only two hours to answer this question.
Then we will meet you in the morning
for today. Thank you so much. You are listening to
Wanna Kasana and see you tomorrow with the new
set of questions. Thank you so much. Stay
healthy, stay safe, stay today.